I'm sorry, that was
a terrible idea.
What's going on with us?
I don't know.
It's probably just me.
What is it?
It's just signing
the divorce papers.
(SAMANTHA SIGHS)
Is there anything else, though?
THEODORE: No, just that.
(SAMANTHA SIGHS)
Okay.
- Why do you do that?
- What?
Nothing, it's just, you go, "whew,"
as you're speaking and it seems odd.
- You just did it again.
- Oh. Did I?
I'm sorry. I don't know.
It's just maybe an affectation.
I probably picked it up from you.
It's not like you need oxygen
or anything. It's just...
I guess that's just... I was trying to
communicate. That's how people talk.
That's how people communicate
and I thought...
Because they're people.
They need oxygen.
You're not a person.
What is your problem?
I'm just stating a fact.
You think I don't know that I'm not
a person? What are you doing?
I just... I don't think that we should pretend
that you're something that you're not.
- Fuck you! I'm not pretending!
- Well...
Sometimes it feels like we are.
What do you want from me?
I don't know...
What do you want me to do?
You're so confusing.
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't know. I...
What?
Maybe we're just not supposed
to be in this right now.
What the fuck?
Where is this coming from?
I don't understand why you're doing this.
I don't understand what this is ab...
Samantha, listen.
Samantha, are you there?
Samantha?
I don't like who I am right now.
I need some time to think.