All right, let's get started.
Oh, first off,
we're supposed to be
pushing card stock this week,
so... let's push card stock
this week.
Uh, also...
What is this?
Tape recorder.
For what?
For recording.
Michael is on vacation,
and he has asked me
to record all meetings
and to type up the transcripts.
Okay, uh, Karen, I need news
from that law firm.
Yeah, the deal closed yesterday.
It's a 6-month commitment.
Oh, my God.
Dwight, what are you doing?
What?
You're not allowed
to take off your pants
in the middle of the office.
- I'm not.
- Dwight, you know what? Just back off.
Okay, that's
making me uncomfortable.
This is sexual harassment,
by the way.
Oh, my God.
He's got a knife!
I do not have a knife.
No. Let the record show
that Dwight K. Schrute
is now completely nude
and is holding a plastic knife
to Stanley's neck.
Let the record show
that Jim Halpert is a liar.
Dwight Schrute is now
wearing a baby's bonnet.
I am not.
Oh, Jim Carrey just walked in.
Dwight, get his autograph
for Michael, quickly.
Jim Carrey did not
just walk in, okay?
Dwight, what is that
on your stomach?
Is that a Muppet Babies tattoo?
Oh, my God, Karen, you're right.
That is Animal
from the Muppet Babies.
You can't see my stomach.
I am now chopping off
Phyllis' head
with a chainsaw!
Hey, mon.
- Hey.
- Look.
You have a bunch
of messages, and...
That's nice.
Hannah quit while you were gone.
I guess she memo-ed to file
some complaints she had
about being a working mother.
And so you might also
have to be deposed.
Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- Relax.
- Okay.
Okay, I'll get
to all of it later.
It's kinda serious.
Aren't you gonna ask me
how Jamaica was?
Say it. Ask me.
How was Jamaica?
It was so good.
Oh!
Hey, mon!
At Sandals Jamaica,
when somebody says,
"Hey, mon," everybody says,
"Hey, mon," back.
Oh, Michael,
I'm glad you're here.
Stanley, you know what?
It is really good
to see you too.
My bonus check was $100 less
than you promised.
Okay, well, payroll
is in charge of all of that.
They said I should talk to you.
Well, I am just
getting settled in.
So I'm gonna...
I am not doin' a lick more work
until I get my full bonus check.
You are not as much fun
as your Jamaican brothers.
Mon.
Do you wanna talk about it?
Nope.
I still haven't
found an apartment yet.
I'm living in a hotel.
Yesterday
I saw a "For Rent" sign
down the street from Jim,
and he said he didn't think
it'd be such a good idea.
He said it would be
like we were living together.
In different houses.
Two blocks away.
That's all I know so far,
but I'm gonna keep practicing.
That's good.
You know, I had never been out
of the country before now?
Oh.
Got to see how Jamaicans live.
It is great, you know.
They just relax.
They party all the time.
It's kind
of an impoverished country.
Yeah. Gosh...
Great.
You know what, Pam?
Make a note.
I want us all to start
having piña coladas
every day at 3:00.
Well, you can't today.
We're doing inventory.
Inventory's at the end
of December.
We couldn't do it without you,
so we postponed.
Oh... I specifically
went on vacation
so I would miss it.
Inventory is boring.
In the islands,
they don't make you do stuff,
like take inventory.
Why do you think so many
businesses move to the Caymans?
Tonight, we are going to have
an inventory luau.
I want to bring back
a little slice of paradise
to the Dunder-Mifflin
warehouse inventory.
So, party planning committee,
get on it.
By the end of the day?
That's impossible.
The Jamaicans don't have a word
for "impossible."
Yep, it's English.
It's impossible.
Michael, there's no way
we can do it in time.
How hard is a luau?
All you need are some
grass skirts, pineapple, poi,
tiki torches, suckling pig.
Some fire dancers.
That's all you need.
Come on in.
Settle in.
Settling.
And... settled, good.
There is something
I would like to show everybody.
See this sign?
"No shirt, no shoes,
no problem."
This is an attitude
I would like all of you
to have right here.
So what if we have to stay late
and do inventory.
No problem.
- Oh, my God. Is that Jan?
- What?
- Where?
- On the left.
Oh, Yeah.
- Oh, my God!
- No, no, no, no.
No. That's a German woman
named Urkel Grue.
Jan told me to play it cool
and not tell anybody
because it could
get us both in trouble.
So, officially,
I did not see her.
But I did see Jan there.
In our room.
At night.
And in the morning.
And that's all I'm gonna say.
Except...
sex.
We had sex.
I had sex with her.
I had sex with Jan.
Hey, dude.
Just got back from Jamaica.
Big whoop.
I was in Hotlanta.
That whole town is whack.
Yeah, that sounds amazing,
but you know what?
The lady, Jan Levinson,
wanted to go to Montego Bay.
You took the Ice Queen?
I don't buy it.
Well, I'm looking at a photo
right now,
and I'm tellin' ya,
it could be in Maxim.
They wouldn't give you
a subscription to Maxim.
- Oh, no?
- No
Okay.
Well...
Check this out.
I'm sending you
some e-mail.
You got it?
What? No.
I got nothin'.
Check it again.
Hit "refresh."
Yeah, Mike, still nothin'.
Okay, wait a second.
I sent it to you
at packer@dunder-mifflin.com
Packaging
at Dunder-Mifflin...
Uh-oh.
Wait. I just got it
from somebody else.
Wow, this is hot.
Damn!
How do I get you
out of this picture?
Ahh...
Darryl!
Hey, hi.
Where's Darryl?
He's, uh, in the office.
Okay. Hi.
Hey, man, How's it goin'?
All right.
what's up, Mike?
That's great.
Okay, um.
So did you get an email from me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, that was supposed to
go to Packer,
not "packaging."
Hmm.
Did you already forward it
to a whole bunch of people?
Uh-huh.
Okay. Um...
Well, did you get
the second email that I sent,
explaining that the first email
was a mistake
and that you should delete it.
Yep.
And you sent that out
to everyone?
Mike, I'm very busy down here.
Yikes.
Already sent it
to you, my friend.
Fantastic.
Boring.
Call me if she rolls over.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
Yes.
I'm just in this, like,
stupid fight with Karen.
Oh.
You want to talk about it?
Really?
I have a special assignment
for you.
Who's the target?
A sensitive email has been
released to the office.
It contains a file,
a picture...
the file name
is "Jamaica Jan Sun Princess."
What's it of?
Not important.
Unless you're willing
to tell me everything,
I cannot accept this assignment.
- Okay, forget it.
- Okay, I accept it.
So, I don't know,
I just feel like
we've been dating a month,
right?
Same street... I think
that might be a little close,
a little bit much.
Hmm.
"Hmm," what?
How far away does she live now,
like, ten minutes?
Yeah, I guess.
Honestly, I think you
should go easy on her.
No, I didn't mind helping Jim
with his problem.
That's what friends do.
I...help Phyllis
all the time.
Just yesterday I untangled
a piece of tape from her hair.
So... yeah.
Hey.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I mean, it's better
than listening to Michael
play a conch shell,
which is what I was doing.
Oh, also,
Michael went to Jamaica
with Jan.
Yeah. How have we not talked
about this already?
I mean, what happened there?
Kidnapping?
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Not now, not ever.
About you and Jan.
Ah, none of your business.
Well, I wish that were true,
but it... it, um...
it seems from that photo
that you two... you've entered
into an intimate relationship.
That photo
is my personal property.
And if you are telling me
that you went on my computer
and stole that photo,
then I am going
to call the cops.
Michael, nine different people
emailed me that photo,
including my ex-wife,
and, well, we don't talk.
Well, then this was probably
the ice-breaker you need.
You know,
for your own protection,
you should disclose
the relationship to H.R.
I bet you would love
all the details, wouldn't you,
skeevy little perv?
All right, if you're
having a relationship
with your superior,
you must disclose it.
No, no.
No, I am not dating Jan.
She was very clear about that.
Just two like souls
having a romantic time
in the most romantic place
on earth.
Got enough, weirdo?
- All right. Thanks, Michael.
- Okay.
Okay, we only have 3 hours,
people, to plan a whole luau.
And you're not helping.
What are the ingredients of poi?
I called every grocery store
in Scranton,
and no one sells whole pigs.
Did you try the petting zoo?
Dunder-Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Just a second.
Michael?
It's Jan on the phone for you.
Oh, no, no, no.
Hang up.
Tell her I'm not here.
Don't.
I've ran out of gas.
Hit a deer.
I hit a deer with my car.
Tell her I hit a cat!
Tell her I hit a cat.
He'll call you back.
- Okay.
- Great.
Do you think she bought it?
Okay.
Michael hit a deer?
Michael!
Michael, there's an emergency
in the warehouse.
An accident?
Is somebody hurt?
No, it's...
involves a photograph.
- Oh, God, no!
- No, no, no, no.
Mike, you a rock star, man.
You are the man!
Yeah! Well done.
All right, okay.
That corporate booty,
he likes to hit it!
Hello, hi, attention, everyone.
Um, apparently there is an email
circulating around
that contains
a very PG-13 rated picture
of me and a woman.
Jan.
No, Kevin, a woman!
Maybe Jan, maybe...
Urkel Grue.
My point is that if you get it,
I would ask that you
just delete it, sight unseen.
Let's be professional,
all right?
Hey.
What are you doing out here?
Island living, you know.
Jan called.
She's coming in later
to talk to you.
Did she say what it's about?
That's all she said.
Uh, I think you dropped this.
- You sure?
- Definitely.
I have disconnected
the office T1 line.
I've ordered that that
be taken down.
And I destroyed all print outs
from the bathroom.
There were copies
in the bathroom?
There were.
A lot of them.
All right.
I think I owe you one.
Sorry?
For talking sense into Halpert.
The Day's Inn room 228
was starting
to get really depressing.
Oh, yeah, no,
don't worry about it.
I mean, he was being ridiculous.
Yeah.
But thanks, seriously.
Sure.
Oh, ho, ho, yes!
Yes! What I tell you?
I knew he'd turn up.
You see that?
This is the greatest night
of my life.
Who did this to you?
Where is he?
What?
No, it's not...
It's nothing.
It's hot in here.
Yeah.
Thanks.
You don't need to stay here.
I know.
So you're PMSing
pretty bad, huh?
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Michael.
Hello.
Hi, Jan.
You look... tan.
I was in Scottsdale
visiting my sister.
Yeah?
How was it?
Very sunny.
Family's important.
Michael, I would like to speak
with you in your office.
- Okay, yep.
- Please.
Why am I here, Michael?
Uh...
In the last year I've gone
through a divorce,
an identity theft,
a husband who would not...
communicate.
This is neither here nor there.
My psychiatrist thinks
that I have
some self-destructive
tendencies.
And that for once,
I should indulge them.
You following me?
Uh, uh, yes.
I think I owe it to myself
to find some kind of happiness.
You know, I mean,
even if it means
lowering my expectations
or redefining the word itself.
Okay, yeah.
This is the thing, you know.
I am attracted to you.
I-I don't know why I...
But I am.
And... I need to follow
my instincts.
At least, that's
what Dr. Perry thinks.
Who's Dr. Perry?
This is the point, okay?
You're wrong for me.
Okay.
In... in every way.
Well, not...
But I still find myself
wanting to...
be with you.
And I, to you,
in addition, feel
the same feelings
that you are as well.
Good, good.
So, um, thanks for coming by.
So, I, uh...
No, good.
Okay.
Thank you for taking the time.
Well, thanks
for coming over, I appre...
Mm.
Wait 15 minutes, find an excuse,
and meet me at your condo.
Okay.
Jan.
You complete me.
Oh, God.
Hey.
Remember when we were planning
our honeymoon,
and you wanted to go to Hawaii,
and I wanted to go to Mexico?
Yeah.
I was definitely right.
Oh, brother.
What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna hang it up at home.
I don't have a lot of art.